<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="matches">
        <item>Alexandra Cabot</item>
        <item>Melody Valentine</item>
        <item>Valerie Brown</item>
        <item>Josie McCoy</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="matches_pic">
        <item>@drawable/alexandra</item>
        <item>@drawable/melody</item>
        <item>@drawable/valerie</item>
        <item>@drawable/josie</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="matches_desc">
        <item>Alexandra is one of the longest-running supporting characters of Josie,
            introduced in the 1960s. She is the twin sister of Alexander Cabot. Both are heirs to Alexander Cabot,
            Jr, a wealthy businessman. Alexandra has black-hair with a white stripe in the middle,
            shaped like a lightning-bolt. She is intelligent but has a cruel side to her personality.
            Back in the 1969, in the storyline introducing the Pussycats music group,
            Alexandra was supposed to be part of the trio with Josie and Melody.
           Alexandra has a personal rivalry with Josie over the affections Alan Mayberry (nicknamed "Alan M").
            She also has a rather poor relationship with her brother .
            At times her mean streak is downplayed and she acts quite friendly with Josie, Melody and Valerie
            in situations which don't involve the band. Another side to her personality was introduced in 1969.
            Her cat Sebastian is the reincarnation of a witchcraft-practicing ancestor of the Cabots.
            When she holds the cat in her hands, Alexandra can cast powerful magic spells.
            Which at times backfire spectacularly. </item>

        <item>Melody was introduced in the Josie stories of the 1960s as one of Josie's friends. Her beauty managed to turn the heads of most males,
            on occasion causing Josie to feel jealous. She was never supposed to be very bright,
            speaking in a sing-song voice, indicated by musical notes added to her word balloons.
            Her dialogue often included silly jokes but also the occasional sharp witticism. </item>

        <item>Valerie Brown is the African-American member of the Pussycats, introduced in 1969. She is the bass player.
            She is the main songwriter of the group and the mechanic responsible for their vehicles.
            Valerie was the tomboy of the trio and often "protected" her teammates from wolfish suitors.
            Her street smarts and intellect could be counted to get them out of difficult situations.</item>

        <item>Josie McCoy is the titular lead of the Josie and the Pussycats series and among the most enduring characters of Archie
            Comics. She was created by Dan DeCarlo in 1958 and named after his wife. Dan tried for a few years to sell the
            character as a comic strip star but eventually settled for offering her to his regular employers at Archie Comics.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>